authorstream.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy on authorSTREAM

###  Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy.

  * We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to a third party for marketing purposes 
  * We will never share your contact information with any other user without your consent. 
  * Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology. 
  * Please note that any presentation, image, or other content posted at the direction of users onto the authorSTREAM sites becomes   
published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice. 

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the authorSTREAM service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices. 

##  Please read this privacy policy to learn more about: 

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by authorSTREAM. 
  * How your personal information is used. 
  * With whom the information may be shared. 
  * How can you access and change your Account information. 
  * What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by authorSTREAM. 
  * How can you contact us. 

##  Information Collection

##  Registration:

In order to use certain features on authorSTREAM Site, you may be required to first create an account on this web site. To create an account you are required to provide the general contact information like name, email address, and choose an account name with authorSTREAM and password.

##  Profile Information:

  * We collect your personal details to maintain your user account on authorSTREAM. Your profile includes general details like your address information, contact phone numbers, and alternate email address. We give you full autonomy to keep this information private or public. These particulars help us maintain your up to date contact information on our records and to serve you better. 
  * Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available, and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload presentations/content or send messages through the authorSTREAM Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any presentations/content that you submit to the authorSTREAM Sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

##  Cookies & Log Files:

Like most web sites, authorSTREAM uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file saved on your computer to allow authorSTREAM to recognize you as a user whenever you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies you will not be able to use our website. Like the information that you enter at registration or in your profile, in the cookie and in the log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.  
One type of cookie, known as a “persistent” cookie, is set once you have logged in to your authorSTREAM account. The next time you visit the authorSTREAM web site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user and thus you need not log in to use the service. In order to access or change any of your private information (like a credit card number), you must log in with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. Additionally, if you log out of the authorSTREAM site in any of your visits you will be prompted to input your password to log in to your authorSTREAM account. Another type of cookie, called a “session” cookie, is used to identify your particular visit to the authorSTREAM site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.  
Complying with the communication standards on the Internet, we automatically receive the URLs of the sites you previously surfed and moved on while your visit to authorSTREAM site. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the authorSTREAM service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

##  Children:

Children can only use our services under the supervision of their parents/legal guardians and we always suggest minors (under the age of 18) not to submit any personal information to us or use the service. authorSTREAM does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the authorSTREAM Sites from persons under 14 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 14. If you are under 14 years of age, then please do not use or access the authorSTREAM Sites at any time or in any manner. If authorSTREAM learns that personally identifiable information of persons less than 14 years of age has been collected on the authorSTREAM Sites without verified parental consent, then authorSTREAM will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

###  Information Use

  * We collect information as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major authorSTREAM Site changes or for customer service purposes). 
  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the authorSTREAM Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 
  * Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual is collected by authorSTREAM from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by authorSTREAM. This information can be utilized by authorSTREAM in such a manner as authorSTREAM, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate. 

##  authorSTREAM Communications:

authorSTREAM will communicate with you through email and notices posted on authorSTREAM website. Please be aware that you will always receive emails from authorSTREAM concerning the proper functioning of your account such as email notices when another user in your network sends you an opportunity. authorSTREAM may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to [ support@authorstream.com](mailto:support@authorstream.com). 

##  Customized Content:

Information you provide at the time of registration or maintain in your Profile is also used to customize your experience on the web site. 

##  Information Sharing

We provide personally identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information to our affiliated companies, subsidiaries, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our privacy policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

##  Sharing Information With Third Parties:

authorSTREAM takes the privacy of its users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third party or parties for marketing purposes. 

In the event that authorSTREAM is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

##  Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services:

authorSTREAM partners with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. Whenever we offer such combined services, it will always be your choice to make use of the combined services or not. In these cases, your personally identifiable information will only be passed from authorSTREAM to our partner if you choose to use the combined service.

##  Legal Disclaimer:

It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

##  Accessing and Changing Your Account Information

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your authorSTREAM account any time by logging in to your account on the authorSTREAM website and editing the information on your Profile page. You can also close your account on the authorSTREAM website. If you close your authorSTREAM account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the authorSTREAM Privacy Policy that you have previously agreed to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the authorSTREAM service, please send your request to [ customer_service@authorstream.com](mailto:customer_service@authorstream.com). Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with authorSTREAM under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to [customer_service@authorstream.com](mailto:customer_service@authorstream.com) within three business days of our receiving it.

##  Security

All private information like your address or credit card number can be accessed only by providing your password.

##  Changes to this Privacy Policy

authorSTREAM may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we process your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

##  Questions or Comments

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@authorSTREAM.com](mailto:privacy@authorstream.com) or contact us at:  
authorSTREAM.com Private Limited  
C-133, Second Floor,  
Industrial Area, PCL Chowk,  
Phase VIII, Mohali-160071, India  
Tel/Fax: +91-172-5013134-35
